Do you know why you guys are bad at math?
(16 days until the final exam)
You don't know the reason.
Without knowing the reason,
you blindly memorize the formulas.
Oh Bum Seok,
you arrived after the class ended.
I'm sorry.
In any case, you should think about
the reason why...
I said those words.
President.
Attention. Bow.
- Thank you.
Bum Seok.
Did you drink?
Bum Seok, are you okay?
You have a mean headache, right?
Yes. I feel so queasy.
I don't remember what happened
towards the end.
You were so funny yesterday.
And Yong Jin, that punk,
totally slept with that girl.
- Really?
- Yes. Don't you remember?
You paid for the motel.
- Did I pay for it?
- Yes.
- You punk.
- You really don't remember.
Let's go for a smoke.
Thanks for the drinks.
Seriously.
We really enjoyed the drinks yesterday.
(Park Ji Hoon)
(Choi Hyun Wook)
(Hong Kyung)
(Lee Yeon)
(Shin Seung Ho)
(Weak Hero Class 1)
(Screenplay and production by Yu Su Min)
(Originated from "Weak Hero"
by Seo Pae Seu and Kim Jin Seok)
Which group are we in?
Group Six.
It's the table at the end.
Didn't Bum Seok come to school yet?
- He did.
- He did? When?
Bum Seok, that girl
touched your thighs so much yesterday.
Seriously.
Hey, you rapped in English at the karaoke.
It was so unexpected.
I guess you have a lot of pent-up anger.
Let's go again.
The three of us should go
without Yong Jin.
Totally. Yong Jin took the girl
when you had a chance with her.
We need to talk.
What's up with you?
What do you mean?
Why didn't you pick up the phone?
What?
I didn't know you called.
What's up with them?
Why did you suddenly become friends
with Lee Jeong Chan and Han Tae Hoon?
I can befriend whomever I like.
You, Soo Ho, and I need to talk.
I have nothing to say.
That punk looked down on me
from the start.
That punk never thought of me as a friend.
He just thought of me as an underling.
You got caught badmouthing me, right?
What are you going to do about it?
- Drink it up!
There you go!
You came.
Bum Seok, it has been a while.
Yes. It has been a while.
- Sit here.
- Yes, sit here.
He is Oh Bum Seok.
He is a friend from my last school.
He is Assemblyman Oh Jin Won's son.
Who's that?
He is an assemblyman.
Really? That's incredible.
They are Seo Hyun, Ji An, and Soo A.
They are from my school.
He is Kang Woo Young.
He is my friend
who will join UFC in the future.
You have heard
of "Physical Therapist Woo Young," right?
What? Physical therapy?
Check it out later.
It's a channel where he spars
with douchebags who claim to be strong.
It's so funny.
Nice to meet you.
Right. Nice to meet you.
By the way, I heard that you parted ways
with Yeon Si Eun and An Soo Ho.
- Yes.
- How did that happen?
You guys were joined at the hip.
Soo Ho thinks he is the king.
Soo Ho is so annoying.
He thinks people are lesser than him.
I need to teach that bastard a lesson.
Whatever. I am sorry about the last time.
- Let's clink our glasses.
- Drink it up.
- Cheers.
I want to transfer
to a different school too.
Isn't he cool?
Some experts.
Some experts estimated...
What did they estimate?
(Daemyung Institute)
Si Eun.
What's this?
Must you ask? It's Friday night.
Let's drive all night long. Come on.
You look cute.
It's Unit 901. Think of it as training
and take the stairs.
- Are you making me work?
- Of course not. Don't hurt my feelings.
I am helping you become fit.
I will be back
after I make another delivery.
Cheers.
Isn't it great?
Is Young Yi working well?
Yes. He has a knack for it.
He gets along with people too.
I think Bum Seok is being used...
by Lee Jeong Chan and Han Tae Hoon.
So what?
I think he buys them shoes and clothes.
Bum Seok pays for the drinks too.
He reeks of alcohol every day.
What if Bum Seok is the one
who is using them?
That punk wanted it from the start.
He latched onto us...
because he wanted to be popular.
He thought hanging out with us
made him cooler.
Do you really believe that?
Did you have fun during the weekend?
Yeong Bin brought pretty girls.
- You traitors.
- I am going to date one of them.
For real?
Stop daydreaming, you lunatic.
It's true love.
She gave me a mysterious look.
She was fascinated to see a high schooler.
You look like an elementary schooler,
okay?
- Bring it on.
- Do you want to have a go at me?
Seo Hyun and I talked afterward.
- Give me a break.
- Stop it, okay?
She sent me a direct message.
She asked to see me on the weekend.
- For real?
- Yes.
How about us?
Maybe I should leave him out.
- Come on. I believe you.
- Ask her to bring Soo A.
- How about us?
- All right. I will ask her.
Ji An. Actually, not Ji An.
- Who else will come?
- Soo A.
Don't overdo it. Three girls are enough.
- Let us join.
- Her profile photo is so pretty.
- Hurry up.
- I will ask her later.
- Come on.
- For real.
- Bum Seok, will you come right away?
All right.
- Bum Seok, I am serious.
- I am sick and tired of him.
- Is he talking about Soo A again?
- Yes!
Please.
Isn't this seat nice?
This seat is really nice.
It's 10 million dollars per 3m².
You have to get me a watch.
- I will treat you this weekend.
- All right.
Not Tae Hoon though.
I am not going to go.
Come on.
We need someone to take on the ugly girl.
Don't take advantage of Bum Seok.
What?
Don't take advantage of him.
- For goodness' sake.
- What nonsense are you spouting?
School is a scary place these days.
You guys buy shoes and drink alcohol...
with Bum Seok's money.
Stop making us the bad guys.
Hey, he wants to pay.
What do you want us to do about it?
I made myself clear.
Let's go and eat.
Stop worrying about Bum Seok.
What?
You have done enough.
I think Bum Seok is behaving that way...
because he is lonely.
I don't know for sure,
but that's my hunch.
- What?
- What are we having for lunch?
I hate perilla leaves.
Who wants to take them off for me?
Hey.
Hey!
What are you guys doing? There is a line.
Get in the line.
I don't get this.
Get in the line, Bum Seok.
I don't want to.
Stop it.
For goodness' sake.
Let's go.
That son of a gun.
That bastard looks down on people.
Hey.
- Is there anyone who can beat him up?
- What?
I can pay.
Is there anyone who can end him?
- I know. Woo Young.
- What?
I watched a few of his videos.
He is really good at fighting.
(Physical Therapist Woo Young)
He would have a chance.
Seriously.
He throws good punches.
How much will you pay me?
How about 1,000 dollars?
And the date?
This Saturday.
An Soo Ho's birthday.
All right then.
I will live stream the fight
without any edits.
- Where are you going?
- Gym.
Sounds great.
By the way, didn't Soo Ho beat him up
back in the day...
at a competition?
That was a long time ago.
Soo Ho left the scene
while Woo Young is still a fighter.
No way.
Hey, you can give him a penalty
if you are so nervous.
Isn't that right?
Delivery is here.
Hey, isn't this it?
I think so.
Here I go. I don't know anymore.
I can't cut it.
I hope I did it right.
Maybe he will die.
I don't care if he dies.
My goodness!
Are you okay?
- Please call 911.
- I am calling them now.
Can you move?
Hey, let's go because we get into trouble.
Bum Seok!
Hurry up!
- I am okay.
- Are you okay?
I am okay.
Shouldn't you go to the hospital?
What did I tell you about
"Cheongsanbyeolgok?"
Are you going to school now?
I am sorry.
Look to the front.
I will wrap it up one last time.
Three meters, divisions, and chorus.
This work shows
the most basic characteristics...
of the Goryeo Period songs.
What happened to your leg?
It's nothing.
Hey.
Don't look at me.
You disgust me.
Get lost.
What was that?
Nothing.
He startled me so much.
Does he know what we did?
How would he know?
He doesn't know, right? There is no way.
Is An Soo Ho's birthday
the day after tomorrow?
All done. Okay.
Gosh, we would have gone to Yangyang
if Soo Ho hadn't gotten into an accident.
Take photos.
Take nice photos.
People would think
that it's your birthday.
Hurry up.
- Come on.
- Slow down.
Come on.
Slow down.
- Hey.
- Punch higher.
Hey.
All right.
Is he still not picking up?
No.
Maybe An Soo Ho blocked you.
The number you have dialed is...
What?
Nothing.
We have more than 30 minutes
before An Soo Ho gets here.
Why are you cooking seaweed soup already?
Seaweed soup gets tastier
if you cook it longer.
Says who?
(Are you at the party room?)
(I am nearby. Can I see you for a second?)
Hey. Didn't you cut ties with Oh Bum Seok?
Did Soo Ho say that?
(Today is Soo Ho's birthday.)
No, he didn't.
Why did you suddenly bring up Bum Seok?
(Please come outside for a second
without telling Si Eun or Soo Ho.)
(I want to give him a present.)
What? It's nothing.
I am going to go to a convenience store.
It has been a while. Have you been well?
Yes.
Have you been well?
I am sorry about the last time.
I put you in a tight spot
by picking up the phone.
Si Eun was really worried about you.
Soo Ho will be here soon.
Let's enter the room together.
I will help you guys make up.
Hey.
You didn't put me in a tight spot.
What can you do?
What?
There is no need for us to make up.
For goodness' sake.
What's this?
If you go that way...
Gosh, don't play in a calculative way.
Listen. Playing a game
is different from studying.
Gosh, hand it over.
Is Young Yi crawling back?
What's taking her so long? I am starving.
We can cut the cake later.
Shall we start eating without her?
Unbelievable.
That's a great idea. I love it.
- I will try calling Young Yi.
- Okay.
The number you have dialed is unavailable.
Please leave a message...
Do you know
that microwaved pizza tastes amazing?
You will be surprised. Just you wait.
(18-3 Bamgogae-ro, Gangnam-gu, Seoul)
(Stop ignoring my calls and come.)
Don't look at me. You disgust me.
Hey, Young Yi isn't the problem.
Hey. Didn't you cut ties with Oh Bum Seok?
I am going to go to a convenience store.
Hey, hurry up and take a seat.
It smells amazing.
Hey. Look at this cheese.
- Hey.
- Go ahead and eat.
Okay.
I want to eat fried chicken too,
but I will suppress the urge.
Okay?
(I am on my way, so wait.)
(Delete)
(Bum Seok is blocked.)
(Slide to power off)
I am going to go to a convenience store.
So suddenly? Hey.
Come back soon. I can't wait
for more than five minutes. I am serious.
I will be back soon. Go ahead and eat.
I really need a smoke.
An Soo Ho didn't answer my calls.
But when he saw your photo,
he said he'd come right away.
Shut your mouth.
Your mouth smells like poop.
Hey, I have a question.
Are you going out with An Soo Ho?
Stop spouting nonsense.
That's how relationships work.
There has to be give and take.
You have no place to stay.
Soo Ho let you sleep in his house...
and gave you a part-time job.
I was wondering what you gave him.
Give me a break.
The Battle of Thermopylae.
To defeat the much bigger army,
Spartans fought at a narrow pass.
When you are fighting against many,
you must make use of the surroundings.
What's this?
Si Eun.
My goodness.
It has been forever, Yeon Si Eun.
What's going on? Where is Soo Ho?
It's so good to see you.
- Let's go.
- What?
For goodness' sake.
Go and catch them.
What's this? Where is An Soo Ho?
For goodness' sake.
Go!
I'll bring the police.
Take this.
- Hurry up.
- Gosh.
Catch them.
Please come here right away.
We are about to get ruined.
- Hey!
- They are coming after me.
Stop right there!
Yeon Si Eun!
You punk!
You little punk.
Hey, hold on.
Hold on.
What a view.
What's this? Where is An Soo Ho?
Are you Yeong Bin's friend?
A weapon won't help you.
How dare you use a weapon?
You dirty bastard.
Stop.
Let him go.
What?
I have no ill feelings toward Yeon Si Eun.
Let him go.
I just need to get An Soo Ho.
That's your problem.
I have many ill feelings toward him.
For goodness' sake. I told you to stop.
You little punk.
Hey.
What?
Everyone is here to help you, you bastard.
Is Yeon Si Eun a friend...
and we aren't?
I told you...
- to know your place.
- Kill him.
Kill him.
Take that, you punk.
You bastard.
Hit his head.
Hey, Oh Bum Seok.
Let's reschedule the fight
against An Soo Ho.
I told my friends all about it.
And transfer the money for today.
I got you one punk.
Did you think you could walk all over us?
My jaw still hurts, you bastard.
Kick him more. Darn it.
You little punk.
Hey, she called the police.
- Hurry up.
- Darn it.
Hurry up.
For goodness' sake.
Hey, you thought you won, right?
Yeon Si Eun.
Hey, Si Eun.
(All firms, characters, locations, names,
and events in this work are fictitious.)
(Any resemblance to actual events
or persons is purely coincidental.)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)